David Dietz Papers
David Dietz Papers
- Correspondence
  - Friedman, Stanley S. (Box 9)
  - Friesen, A. P. (Box 9)
  - Fuerst, John J. (Box 9)
  - Fuller and Smith and Ross Incorporated (Box 27)
  - G, general (Box 9)
  - Galdston, Iago (Dr.) (Box 9)
  - Gallo, Joaquin (Dr.) (Box 27)
  - Gandola, Frank (Box 9)
  - Garfield, James R. (Box 9)
  - Garrett, Paul (formerly with General Motors) (Box 27)
  - [D. J.] Garson and Son Incorporated (Box 9)
  - Gates, Arnold F. (Box 9)
  - Gaynor, Leonard (Box 27)
  - Gebbard, Bruno (Dr.) (Box 9)
  - Gee, Haldane (Dr.) (Box 9)
  - Geiger, H. Jack (Dr.) (Box 9)
  - Geiger, J. C. (Dr.) (Box 9)
  - Geismer, Alan S. (Box 9)
  - General Electric Company, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - General Electric Radio Programs (Box 9)
  - General Motors Corporation (Box 9)
  - Geological Survey, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Gerard, R. W. (Box 9)
  - German American Congress for Democracy (Box 9)
  - Gernsback Publications, Incorporated (Box 9)
  - Gerwig, George W. (Box 9)
  - Getts, Clark H. (Box 9)
  - [John] Gill and Sons Company (Box 9)
  - Gill, Robert S. (Box 9)
  - Ginn, Robert M. (Box 9)
  - Ginsburgh, A. Robert (Colonel) (Box 9)
  - Ginsburgh, A. Robert (Colonel), additional material (Box 27)
  - Gitman, Carolyn L. (Box 27)
  - Gittelsohn, Roland B. (Rabbi) (Box 9)
  - Glass, Michael E. (Box 9)
  - Glass, Michael E., additional material (Box 27)
  - Glasser, Melvin A. (Box 27)
  - Glasser, Otto (Box 27)
  - Glasstone, Samuel (Box 27)
  - Glenbrook Laboratories (Box 27)
  - Glenn, John (Senator) (Box 9)
  - Glennan, T. Keith (Dr.) (Box 9)
  - Glueck, Nelson (Dr.) (Box 27)
  - Goddard, Dick (Box 9)
  - Goldblatt, Harry (Dr.), 3 folders (Box 9)
  - Goldblatt, Maurice (Box 27)
  - Goldfield, E. R. (Box 9)
  - Golub, J. J. (Dr.) (Box 9)
  - Gonzalez, Manuel (Dr.) (Box 9)
  - Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company, 3 folders (Box 9)
  - Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company, additional material (Box 27)
  - Gordon, Henry C. (Box 9)
  - Goudsmit, Sam A. (Dr.) (Box 27)
  - Grace and Bement (Box 9)
  - Grady Award (Box 9)
  - Grant, David N. W. (Brigadier General) (Box 10)
  - Gray, R. W. (Box 10)
  - Grauer, Ben (Box 27)
  - Great Lakes Exposition (Box 10)
  - Greater Cleveland Association Foundation (Box 27)
  - Greenberg Publisher, New York (Box 10)
  - Greenblatt, Robert B. (Dr.) (Box 10)
  - Gteenfield, George (Box 27)
  - Greene, Edmund (Box 10)
  - Greenstein, Jesse L. (Dr.) (Box 10)
  - [W. L.] Gregory Educational Museum (Box 10)
  - Greneker, G. P. (Box 10)
  - Gries, Robert Hays (Box 10)
  - Griffith Observatory (Box 10)
  - Grill, G. W. (Lakewood Schools) (Box 27)
  - Griswold-Eschleman Company (Box 10)
  - Grolier Society (Box 10)
  - Gross, Gerald (Box 27)
  - Gross, Jerome (Dr.) (Box 27)
  - Grossberg, Maurice H. (M.D.) (Box 10)
  - Grossman, Leo, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Grossman, Marc J. (Box 10)
  - Groves, Leslie R. (Lieutenant General) (Box 10)
  - Grunewald, A. C. (Internal Revenue Service) (Box 10)
  - Guggenheim, Henry F. (Box 10)
  - Gulf Oil Corporation (Box 10)
  - Gund, George (Box 10)
  - Gyorgy, Paul (Dr.) (Box 10)
  - H, general (Box 10)
  - Haas, R. V. (Box 27)
  - Hagedoorn, A. (Dr.) (Box 10)
  - Hale, George (Dr.) Ellery, Mount Wilson Observatory (Box 10)
  - Halle, Day (Box 27)
  - Hamlin, Chauncey (Buffalo Museum of Science) (Box 10)
  - Hanna, Gordon (Box 10)
  - Harper, J. (Dr.) (Box 10)
  - Harper and Brothers (Box 10)
  - Harper and Row (Box 10)
  - Harris, Dick (Box 10)
  - Harris, John (Box 27)
  - Hart, Henry (Box 10)
  - [John A.] Hartford Foundation (Box 10)
  - Hartwell (Jr.), Shattuck Wellman (M.D.) (Box 10)
  - Harvard College Observatory (Box 10)
  - Harvard University (Box 10)
  - Harvard University Press (Box 10)
  - Haslett, Arthur W. (Box 10)
  - Havens, Munson (Box 10)
  - Hawaii (State) (Box 10)
  - Hawaii trip, 1965; miscellaneous correspondence (Box 10)
  - Hawaii Visitors Bureau (Box 10)
  - Hawkins, William W. (Box 10)
  - Hayes, Ralph (Box 27)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, Department of (Box 10)
  - Health News Institute (Box 10)
  - Heavillin, J. Seegar (Box 27)
  - Hebrew Union College (Box 10)
  - Hebrew University (Box 10)
  - Hellerstein, Herman K. (Dr.) (Box 10)
  - Henderson, Ralph B. (Box 27)
  - Henry, Marcia (Box 10)
  - Henry Ford Hospital (Box 10)
  - Henry, Thomas R. (Box 27)
  - Henwood, Stanley E. (Box 10)
  - Hercules Powder Company (Box 10)
  - Herman, Alexander C. (Box 10)
  - Hertz, Roy (Dr.) (Box 10)
  - Herzmark, Maurice H. (Dr.) (Box 10)
  - Heslep, Charter (Dr.) (Box 10)
  - Higbee Company (Box 10)
  - Highlights for Children, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Hill, Ed (Box 27)
  - Hill and Knowlton (Box 27)
  - Hills, Lee, 2 folders (Box 10)
  - Himler, Mary Rose [empty folder] (Box 11)
  - Hintz, Walter J. (Box 11)
  - Hodgman, Charles D. (Editor, Handbook of Chemistry and Physics) (Box 11)
  - Hoftyzer, Ernest (Box 27)
  - Hollywood Sun Tatler (Box 11)
  - Holt, Rinehart and Winston (Box 11)
  - Holy Blossom Temple (Box 11)
  - Hoover, Earl R. (Box 11)
  - Horizons Research Incorporated (Box 11)
  - [Joseph] Horne Company (Box 11)
  - Houghton Mifflin Company (Box 11)
  - Houssay, B. A. (Dr.) (Box 11)
  - Hovorka, Frank (Dr.) (Box 11)
  - Howard, Jack R. (Box 11)
  - Howard, Jack (Box 11)
  - Howard, Mrs. Lelila G. (Box 27)
  - Howard, N. R. (Box 11)
  - Howard, Roy W., 3 folders (Box 11)
  - Howarth, Tony (Box 11)
  - Howe, Charles Sumner (Dr.) (President Emeritus, Case) (Box 11)
  - Howe, H. E. (Editor, Industrial and Engineering Chemistry) (Box 11)
  - Howell, Ruth (Box 11)
  - Hoyle, Fred (Box 11)
  - Humel, Dorothy (Box 11)
  - Humphrey, Hubert (U.S. Vice President) (Box 11)
  - Hungarian Quarterly (Box 11)
  - Hutchinson, Veronica (Box 27)
  - Huxley, Julian (Dr.) (Box 11)
  - I, general (Box 11)
  - India Information Services (Box 27)
  - Indiana State Board of Health (Box 11)
  - Indiana University (Box 11)
  - Indiana University Medical Center (Box 11)
  - Indianapolis Times (Box 27)
  - Ingalls, Albert G. (Box 11)
  - Institute for Scientific Information (Box 27)
  - Inter-Agency Seminar on Hospital Administration (Box 11)
  - International Atomic Energy Agency (Box 11)
  - International Business Machines Corporation (Box 11)
  - International Polio Congress (Medical Reports) (Box 11)
  - International Polio Congress, 1957 (Box 11)
  - International Poliomyelitis Congress (Box 11)
  - International Platform Association (Box 11)
  - International Press-Cutting Bureau (Box 11)
  - International Press Institute (Box 27)
  - International Year Book and Statesmen's Who's Who (Box 11)
  - Interscience Publishers, Incorporated (Box 27)
  - Iron Age (Box 11)
  - Irvin, John L. (Box 11)
  - Israel (Box 11)
  - Israeli Consulate (Box 11)
  - Israeli Embassy (Box 11)
  - J, general (Box 11)
  - Jackson, Henry M. (Box 11)
  - Jackson, Perry B. (Honorable) (Box 11)
  - Jackson Memorial Laboratory, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Jaffe, S. J. (Box 11)
  - Jamaica (Box 11)
  - Jancura, Charlene (Box 11)
  - Jaques Cattell Press (Box 11)
  - Jaslin, Joseph (Rabbi) (Box 28)
  - Jasper, Herbert H. (Dr.) (Box 11)
  - Jeffries, Zay (Dr.) (Box 11)
  - Jewish Community Federation of Cleveland (Box 11)
  - John, Betty (Box 28)
  - John Carroll University, 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Johns Hopkins University (Box 11)
  - Johnson, Ewing (Box 12)
  - Johnson, J. Kimball (Box 12)
  - Johnson, Mary Catherine (Box 12)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B. (U.S. President) (Box 28)
  - Johnston, John M. (Box 28)
  - Jones, A. L. (Dr.) (Box 12)
  - Jones, Paul (Box 12)
  - Jones, Paul K. (Mayor) (Box 12)
  - Jones, W. Powell (Dr.) (Box 12)
  - Junior Astronomy Club (Box 28)
  - Justice, Department of (Box 12)
  - K, general (Box 12)
  - Kaempffert, Waldemar (science editor) (Box 28)
  - Kaiser Engineers (Box 28)
  - Kalish, Alice N. (Box 12)
  - Kalish, Max (Box 12)
  - Kalish, Richard (Box 12)
  - Kamm, Herb (Box 12)
  - Kane, James M. (Box 12)
  - Karamu House (Box 12)
  - Karsner, Howard T. (Professor of Pathology, WRU) (Box 12)
  - Katz, Louis N. (Dr.), 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Kaufman, David E. (Box 12)
  - Keedick, Lee (Box 12)
  - Keller, Helen (Box 12)
  - Kelly, Michael A. (Box 28)
  - Kenen, I. L. (Box 12)
  - Kennedy, Ed (Senator) (Box 12)
  - Kent, Fraser (Box 12)
  - Kent State University, 2 folders (Box 12)
  - Kent State University, additional material (Box 28)
  - Kentucky Post and Times-Star (Box 12)
  - Kern, Janet (Box 28)
  - Kessler, Lillian (Box 28)
  - Kiplinger, Austin (Box 12)
  - Kiplinger, Washington editors (Box 28)
  - Kirkwood, Marie (Western Reserve University) (Box 12)
  - Kirsch, R. Alain (Box 12)
  - Klein, Howard (Box 12)
  - Kitt Peak National Observatory (Box 12)
  - Kitts, Carroll H. (Box 12)
  - Kiwanis Club (Box 28)
  - Klein, Harold C. (Dr.) (Box 12)
  - Knopf, Alfed A. (Box 12)
  - Knopf, Alfed A., additional material (Box 28)
  - Knoxville News-Sentinel (Box 12)
  - Korber, Susan (Dr.) (Box 28)
  - Korff, Serge A. (Dr.) (Box 28)
  - Korn, Bertram W. (Rabbi) (Box 12)
  - Kornbetg, Arthur (Box 12)
  - Kovener, Lola (Box 28)
  - Kranzberg, Melvin (Box 28)
  - Krieghbaum, Hillier (Box 12)
  - Krieghbdum, Hillier (Dr.) (Box 12)
  - Krogman, Wilton Marion (Box 12)
  - Kupier, Gerard P. (Dr.) (Box 12)
  - L, general (Box 12)
  - Laboratory of Anthropology, Santa Fe, New Mexico (Box 12)
  - LaFave, Arthur (Box 28)
  - de Lafond, Anne (Box 28)
  - Lahey Clinic (Box 12)
  - Lal, Gobind Behari (Box 12)
  - Lal, Gobind (Box 12)
  - Lalor Foundation (Box 28)
  - Lamberton, Clark D. (Box 12)
  - Landon, Paris (Box 12)
  - Landauer, Kenneth (Dr.) (Box 28)
  - Lanin, Lester (Box 28)
  - Lapp, R. E. (Dr.) (Box 12)
  - Lark-Horovitiz, K. (Dr.) (Purdue University) (Box 12)
  - Laronge, Tom (Box 28)
  - Larrick, Nancy (Box 12)
  - Lasker, Mrs. Albert D. (Box 12)
  - Lasker Awards (Box 12)
  - Laurence, William L. (Box 12)
  - Lausche, Frank J. (Senator) (Box 12)
  - Laycock, George (Box 12)
  - Leake, Chauncey (Dr.) (Box 12)
  - Leary, James C. (Box 28)
  - Lebensohn, Zigmond M. (Dr.) (Box 12)
  - Leckrone, Walter (Box 12)
  - Lecture dates (Box 28)
  - Lederle Laboratories (Box 28)
  - Lee, Fitzhugh (Captain) (Box 28)
  - Leech, Edward T. ( The Pittsburgh Press) (Box 12)
  - Leedy, Denoe (Box 12)
  - Lehenbquer, Albert (Box 12)
  - Leick, William (Box 12)
  - Leith, Charles Kenneth ( Mineral Inquiry) (Box 12)
  - Lelyveld, Arthur J. (Rabbi) (Box 12)
  - Leoni's "Quo Vadis" Restaurant (Box 12)
  - Lengel, William C. (Editor, Liberty Magazine) (Box 12)
  - Lennen and Mitchell, Incorporated (Box 12)
  - Letters (Box 12)
  - Letters, additional material (Box 28)
  - Leutner, W. G. (Box 13)
  - Levinthal, Sonia (Box 13)
  - Lewis, Boyd (NEA Service, Incorporated) (Box 13)
  - Lewis Research Center (Box 13)
  - Lewis, Verna M. (Box 28)
  - Lewis, Warner (Box 28)
  - Libby, W. F. (Dr.) (Box 13)
  - Liberty Tricks of Trade (Box 13)
  - Library Presidents (Box 13)
  - Lieberman, Helen and Moses (Box 13)
  - Lightning, Ball (Box 13)
  - Lillienthal, David E. (Box 28)
  - Limestone College (Box 28)
  - Lincoln Electric Company (Box 13)
  - Lindley, Betty (Box 13)
  - Lindsley, Donald B. (Dr.) (Box 13)
  - [M. C.] Link Foundation (Box 13)
  - [J. B.] Lippincott Company (Box 13)
  - Literary Clipping Service (Box 13)
  - Littell, Robert (Box 13)
  - [Arthur D.] Little Incorporated (Box 13)
  - Little, Brown and Company (Box 13)
  - Lockhart, Jack (Box 13)
  - Loesser, Arthur (Box 28)
  - London, 1972 (Box 13)
  - Long, Fern (Dr.) (Box 13)
  - Long and Smith, Incorporated (Box 13)
  - Long, S. W. (Box 13)
  - Los Alamos Scientific Laboratory (Box 13)
  - Lott, Dwight W. (Box 13)
  - Love, John (Box 28)
  - Lovell, A. C. B. (Box 13)
  - Lucas, Jim G. (Box 28)
  - Luckiesh, Matthew (Dr.) (Box 28)
  - Luisada, A. (Dr.) (Box 28)
  - Lull, George F. (Major General) (Box 13)
  - Lutgens, Harry (Major) (Box 13)
  - Luton, Barbara (Box 13)
  - Lyon, George H. (Box 13)
  - MacAfee, Larry (General) (Box 13)
  - McAllister, Ralph (Box 13)
  - McBride, Mary Margaret (Box 13)
  - McCann-Erickson, Incorporated (Box 13)
  - McCuskey, Sidney W. (Dr.) (Box 13)
  - McDonald Observatory (Box 13)
  - McDonough, Gordon L. (Rep.) (Box 13)
  - McDonough, Steve (Box 28)
  - MacDougal, D. T. (Dr.) (Box 13)
  - Macelwance, James B. (S.J.) (Box 28)
  - McGill, Ralph (Box 13)
  - McGrady, Patrick M. (Box 13)
  - McGovern, George (Senator) (Box 13)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company (Box 13)
  - McGraw-Hill Book Company (W.R.E. Baxter) (Box 13)
  - McGregor, J. B. (Dr.) (Columbia University) (Box 13)
  - McIntire, Ruth (Oglebay Park, Wheeling, West Virginia) (Box 13)
  - [David] McKay Company, Incorporated (Box 13)
  - MacKinnon-Fly Publications, Incorporated (H. J. Brown, Jr., Vice President) (Box 13)
  - MacLeish, Archibald (Box 13)
  - MacMillan, W. D. (Dr.) (University of Chicago) (Box 13)
  - MacMillan Company (Box 13)
  - MacMurray, Claire (Box 28)
  - McNutt, Paul V. (Honorable) (Box 13)
  - M, general (Box 13)
  - Madow, Leo (Dr.) (Box 13)
  - Magnuson, Warren G. (Senator) (Box 13)
  - Magnuson Commission (Box 28)
  - Mahoney, Tom (Box 28)
  - Maisel, Albert Q. (Box 13)
  - Major, John K. (Dr.) (Box 13)
  - Manchester Guardian (Box 28)
  - Mandel, Morton L. (Box 13)
  - Mann, Martin (Box 13)
  - Marcus, Robert L. (Dr.) (Box 13)
  - Markham, John (Box 13)
  - Marmaraton, Jessie (Dr.) (Box 13)
  - Marmorston, Jessie (Dr.) (Box 28)
  - Marvin, Theodore (Box 28)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Box 14)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Karl T. Compton, President) (Box 14)
  - Masserman, Theodore (Dr.) (Box 28)
  - Massey, Albert G. (Box 14)
  - Maternal Health Association (Mrs. Eugene Freedheim) (Box 28)
  - Mather, Kirtley F. (Professor, Harvard Scientific Book Club) (Box 28)
  - Matson, Carlton K. (Box 14)
  - May Company (Box 14)
  - Mayo, Leonard W. (Dr.) (Box 14)
  - Medical and Pharmaceutical Information Bureau (Box 14)
  - Medical Care Project (Box 14)
  - Medical letters (Box 14)
  - Medical picture (Box 14)
  - Medical Tribune (Box 14)
  - Mediterranean tour (Box 14)
  - Meeman, Edward J. (Box 14)
  - Mellon Institute of Industrial Research (Box 14)
  - Meltzer, Milton (Box 14)
  - Memorial Center for Cancer and Allied Diseases (Box 14)
  - Mencken, H. L. (Editor, The American Mercury) (Box 14)
  - Menninger Foundation, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Menzel, Donald H. (Dr.) (Box 14)
  - Merck and Company (Box 14)
  - Merriam, John C. (Dr.) (President, Carnegie Institution of Washington) (Box 14)
  - Merryfield, M.R. (Box 28)
  - Mesnick, Harry (Box 14)
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art (Box 14)
  - Metzenbaum, Howard M. (Box 14)
  - Mexico (Box 14)
  - Miami Daily News (Box 14)
  - Michael Reese Hospital (Box 14)
  - Military surgeons (Box 14)
  - Millard, Walter J. (Box 14)
  - Miller, Clyde R. (Box 14)
  - Miller, Clyde R., additional material (Box 28)
  - Miller, Clyde R. (Dr.) (Box 14)
  - Miller, Dayton C. (Professor) (Box 14)
  - Miller, Loye W. (Box 14)
  - Millikan, Robert A. (Dr.) (Pasadena, California) (Box 14)
  - Millikan, Robert A. (Dr.) (Box 14)
  - Milliken, W. M. (Cleveland Museum of Art) (Box 14)
  - Millis, John (Box 14)
  - Mitts, James E. (Box 14)
  - Mirsky, I. Arthur (Dr.), 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Molesworth, Gordon R. (Box 14)
  - Moley, Raymond, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Montreal (Box 14)
  - [Donald] Morgan Associates (Box 14)
  - Morgan, William Wilson (Dr.) (Box 14)
  - Morrill, James L. (Dr.) (Box 14)
  - [Philip] Morris Incorporated (Box 14)
  - [William] Morrow and Company (Box 14)
  - Morse, Philip M. (Dr.) (Box 14)
  - Moulton, F. R. (Dr.) (Box 14)
  - Mount Sinai Hospital, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Mount Union College (Box 14)
  - Mount Wilson-Palomar (Box 14)
  - Moynahan, John (Colonel) (Box 14)
  - Munro, Thomas (Box 14)
  - Murphy, Walter J. (Box 14)
  - Musical Arts Association (Box 14)
  - Muskie, Edmund S. (Senator) (Box 14)
  - Myers, Max (Box 14)
  - Myers, J. L., (Professor, Oxford) (Box 14)
  - N, general (Box 15)
  - NASA (Box 15)
  - Nansen, Fridtjof (Dr.), lecture (Box 15)
  - Nassau (Box 15)
  - Nassau, J. J. (Box 15)
  - Nassau, J. J. (Professor) (Box 15)
  - Nathanson, S. Allen (Box 15)
  - National Advisory Committee for Aeronautics (Box 15)
  - National Apple Institute (Box 15)
  - National Association for Mental Health (Box 15)
  - National Association of Science Writers, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - National Association of Science Writers, additional material (Box 28)
  - National Broadcasting Company (Box 15)
  - National Carbon Company (Box 15)
  - National City Bank (Box 15)
  - National Concert and Artists Corporation (Box 15)
  - National Council of Jewish Women (Box 15)
  - National Council of Teachers of English (Box 15)
  - National Federation of Temple Brotherhoods (Box 15)
  - National Foundation, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis, Incorporated (Box 15)
  - National Fund for Medical Education (Box 15)
  - National Geographic Society (Box 15)
  - National Health Council (Box 15)
  - National Health Education Committee (Box 15)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (Box 15)
  - National Institutes of Health (Box 15)
  - National Jewish Hospital at Denver (Box 15)
  - National Malleable and Steel Castings Company (Box 15)
  - National Mental Health Committee (Box 15)
  - National Multiple Sclerosis Society (Box 15)
  - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (Box 15)
  - National Park Service (Box 15)
  - National Policy Committee (Box 15)
  - National Press Club (Box 15)
  - National Radio Astronomy Observatory (Box 15)
  - National Research Council, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - National Roster of Scientific and Specialized Personnel (Box 15)
  - National Science Foundation (Box 15)
  - National Society for Medical Research (Box 15)
  - National Society for the Prevention of Blindness, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - National Sugar Refining Company (Box 15)
  - National Tuberculosis Association, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Naval Ordnance Laboratory (Box 15)
  - NEA Service, Incorporated (Box 15)
  - Needham, Harper and Steers, Incorporated (Box 15)
  - Negus, Sidney (Box 15)
  - Negus, Sidney S. (Dr.) (Box 15)
  - Neill Letter (Box 16)
  - Netherlands Information Service (Box 16)
  - Neville, Glenn (Box 16)
  - New Home Library (Box 16)
  - New Jersey Zinc Company (Box 16)
  - "New Outline of Science", reviews (Box 16)
  - New York Academy of Medicine (Box 16)
  - New York Academy of Sciences (Box 16)
  - New York Air Brake Company (Box 16)
  - New York Central System (Box 16)
  - New York Herald Tribune (Box 16)
  - New York State Medical Society (Box 16)
  - New York Tuberculosis and Health Association (Box 16)
  - New York World-Telegram (Box 16)
  - New Yorker (Box 16)
  - Newman, J. S. (Box 16)
  - Nichols, Herbert B., 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Nieman Foundation, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Nininger, H. H. (Dr.) (Box 16)
  - Nixon, Richard (U.S. President) (Box 16)
  - Noonday Press (Box 16)
  - North, Sterling (Box 16)
  - North Ohio Pediatric Society (Box 16)
  - Northwestern University (Box 16)
  - [W.W.] Norton and Company, Incorporated (Box 16)
  - Nova Scotia Public Archives (Box 16)
  - Noyes and Sproul, Incorporated (Box 16)
  - O, general (Box 16)
  - Oakley Jr., Godfrey P. (M.D.) (Box 16)
  - Oberlin College (Box 16)
  - O'Connor, Basil, 4 folders (Box 16)
  - Odenbach, F. L. (Reverend Fr.) (Box 16)
  - Office of Saline Water (Box 16)
  - Office of Surgeon General (Box 16)
  - Office of War Information (Box 16)
  - Ohio Academy of Science (Rush Elliot) (AAAS) (Box 16)
  - Ohio Academy of Science (Box 16)
  - Ohio Historical Society (Box 16)
  - Ohio Newspaper Women's Association (Box 16)
  - Ohio State University (Box 16)
  - Ohio Story (Box 16)
  - Ohioana Library Association (Box 16)
  - Ohmann, O. A. (Dr.) (Box 16)
  - Olaf-Hansen, Erik (Box 16)
  - Oldrive, Robert E. (Box 16)
  - Omansky, Jacob (Box 16)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa Society (Box 16)
  - Opinion Research Corporation (Box 16)
  - Oppenheimer, Michael A. (Rabbi) (Box 16)
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert (Dr.) (Box 16)
  - Orient Tour (Box 16)
  - Oxford University Press (Box 16)
  - Pace, D. P. (Lieutenant Colonel) (Box 17)
  - Pacific Science Center (Box 17)
  - Page, Irvine H. (M.D.) (Box 17)
  - Page, Thornton (Dr.) (Box 17)
  - Palm Springs (Box 17)
  - Pan American World Airways (Box 17)
  - Parke Davis and Company (Box 17)
  - Parker, George B., 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Parron Jr., T. H. (Dr.) (Box 17)
  - Patterson, Don D. (Director, National Advertising Department, Scripps-Howard Newspapers) (Box 17)
  - Pauling, Linus (Dr.) (Box 17)
  - Pearl, Carleton (Box 17)
  - Pendray and Company (Box 17)
  - Pennsylvania State College (Box 17)
  - Pennsylvania State University (Box 17)
  - Perkin-Elmer (Box 17)
  - Perla, David (Dr.) (Box 17)
  - Peters, Richard, 125 Barclay Street (15) (Box 17)
  - Pfeiffer, John (Box 17)
  - Pfizer and Company (Box 17)
  - Philbrick, Shailer S. (Box 17)
  - Phoenix, Arizona (Box 17)
  - Picker X-ray Corporation (Box 17)
  - Pickering, James S. (Dr.) (Box 17)
  - Pillemer, Louis (Professor) (Box 17)
  - Pines, Eunice K. (Box 17)
  - Pittsburgh Press (Box 17)
  - P, general (Box 17)
  - Pittsburgh Press - Leech (Box 17)
  - Planned Parenthood (Box 17)
  - Plohr, H. Warren (Box 17)
  - Plymouth Cordage Company (Box 17)
  - Pocket Magazine (Box 17)
  - Poole, Lynn (Box 17)
  - Popular Mechanics magazine (Box 17)
  - Population Reference Bureau (Box 17)
  - Porter, Philip W. (Box 17)
  - Porter, William N. (Major General) (Box 17)
  - Portis, Sidney A. (Dr.) (Box 17)
  - Portsmouth Times (Box 17)
  - Portz, Matt (Box 17)
  - Post, Herbert (Box 17)
  - Postgraduate medicine (Box 17)
  - Potter, Robert D. (Box 17)
  - Potter, Robert D., additional material (Box 28)
  - Prentice-Hall, Incorporated (Box 17)
  - Press Club (Box 17)
  - Preston, Howard (Box 17)
  - Priestley Memorial Association (Box 17)
  - Prince Edward Island (Box 17)
  - Princeton University (Box 17)
  - Princeton University Press (Box 17)
  - Public Affairs Committee, Incorporated (Box 17)
  - Public Relations Services Limited (Box 17)
  - Publishers (miscellaneous) (Box 17)
  - Pulitzer clippings (Box 17)
  - Pulitzer Prize, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - Pulitzer Prize Committee (Box 17)
  - Pulse of the Nation (Box 18)
  - Pyramid Publications (Box 18)
  - Questar Corporation (Box 18)
  - Quimby, Arthur (Box 18)
  - R, general (Box 18)
  - Radio broadcasts (Box 18)
  - Radio Corporation of America (Box 18)
  - Ramos, Alberto R. (Dr.) (Box 18)
  - Rand, H. J. (Box 18)
  - Random House
    - 1970- (Box 18)
    - Sean Morrison (Box 18)
    - 1968-1969 (Box 18)
    - 1960-1969 (Box 18)
  - Rand McNally and Company (Box 18)
  - Raper, J. W. (Jack) (Box 18)
  - Reardon, Harriet (Box 18)
  - Reichl, Miriam (Box 18)
  - Rein, Michael F. (Box 18)
  - Reines, Frederick (Box 18)
  - Reinthal, Arthur J. (Box 18)
  - Remenyi, Frederick (Box 18)
  - Republic Steel Corporation (Box 18)
  - Research Board for National Security (Box 18)
  - Rhoads, C. P. (Dr.) (Box 18)
  - Richardson, Robert S. (Box 18)
  - Ringwall, Rudolph (Box 18)
  - Rivers, Thomas M. (Dr.) (Box 18)
  - Robbins, Fred C. (Dr.) (Box 18)
  - Robbins, Jr., John C. (Box 18)
  - Robertson, H. P. (Dr.) (Box 18)
  - Rockefeller, Laurence S. (Box 18)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Box 18)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (Box 18)
  - Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research (Box 18)
  - Rockefeller University (Box 18)
  - Rockefeller University Press (Box 18)
  - Rose, William Ganson (Box 18)
  - Rome meeting (Box 18)
  - [Henry] Romeike and Company (Box 18)
  - Roney, Burr (Box 18)
  - Rosenfeld, Sam (Box 18)
  - Rosenthal, Rudolph (Rabbi) (Box 18)
  - Rosinski, Herbert (Dr.) (Box 18)
  - Rostock, Frank W. ( Cincinnati Post) (Box 18)
  - Roth, Mrs. Benjamin (Box 18)
  - Roth, Stanley L. (Marine Sergeant) (Box 18)
  - Rous, Peyton (Dr.) (Box 18)
  - Rousuck, Judy (Box 18)
  - Rowfant Club (Box 18)
  - Roy, Klaus G. (Box 18)